<?xml version = '1.0' encoding = 'UTF-8'?>
<BIDocument class="oracle.dbtools.crest.model.businessinfo.BIDocument" name="CRR, Article 178" directorySegmentName="seg_0" id="0211B933-0A94-9101-AE9C-575039DE34E3">
<createdBy>lindomi</createdBy>
<createdTime>2022-04-06 13:17:00 UTC</createdTime>
<comment><![CDATA[Default of an obligor
1. A default shall be considered to have occurred with regard to a particular obligor when either or both of the following have taken place:
(a) the institution considers that the obligor is unlikely to pay its credit obligations to the institution, the parent undertaking or any of its subsidiaries in full, without recourse by the institution to actions such as realising security;
(b) the obligor is past due more than 90 days on any material credit obligation to the institution, the parent undertaking or any of its subsidiaries. Competent authorities may replace the 90 days with 180 days for exposures secured by residential or SME commercial real estate in the retail exposure class, as well as exposures to public sector entities). The 180 days shall not apply for the purposes of Article 127.
In the case of retail exposures, institutions may apply the definition of default laid down in points (a) and (b) of the first subparagraph at the level of an individual credit facility rather than in relation to the total obligations of a borrower.
2. The following shall apply for the purposes of point (b) of paragraph 1:
(a) for overdrafts, days past due commence once an obligor has breached an advised limit, has been advised a limit smaller than current outstandings, or has drawn credit without authorisation and the underlying amount is material;
(b) for the purposes of point (a), an advised limit comprises any credit limit determined by the institution and about which the obligor has been informed by the institution;
(c) days past due for credit cards commence on the minimum payment due date;
(d) materiality of a credit obligation past due shall be assessed against a threshold, defined by the competent authorities. This threshold shall reflect a level of risk that the competent authority considers to be reasonable;
(e) institutions shall have documented policies in respect of the counting of days past due, in particular in respect of the re- ageing of the facilities and the granting of extensions, amendments or deferrals, renewals, and netting of existing accounts. These policies shall be applied consistently over time, and shall be in line with the internal risk management and decision processes of the institution.
3. For the purpose of point (a) of paragraph 1, elements to be taken as indications of unlikeliness to pay shall include the following:
(a) the institution puts the credit obligation on non-accrued status;
(b) the institution recognises a specific credit adjustment resulting from a significant perceived decline in credit quality subsequent to the institution taking on the exposure;
(c) the institution sells the credit obligation at a material credit- related economic loss;
(d) the institution consents to a distressed restructuring of the credit obligation where this is likely to result in a diminished financial obligation caused by the material forgiveness, or postponement, of principal, interest or, where relevant fees. This includes, in the case of equity exposures assessed under a PD/LGD Approach, distressed restructuring of the equity itself;
(e) the institution has filed for the obligor's bankruptcy or a similar order in respect of an obligor's credit obligation to the institution, the parent undertaking or any of its subsidiaries;
(f) the obligor has sought or has been placed in bankruptcy or similar protection where this would avoid or delay repayment of a credit obligation to the institution, the parent undertaking or any of its subsidiaries.
4. Institutions that use external data that is not itself consistent with the definition of default laid down in paragraph 1, shall make appropriate adjustments to achieve broad equivalence with the definition of default.
5. If the institution considers that a previously defaulted exposure is such that no trigger of default continues to apply, the institution shall rate the obligor or facility as they would for a non-defaulted exposure. Where the definition of default is subsequently triggered, another default would be deemed to have occurred.
6. EBA shall develop draft regulatory technical standards to specify the conditions according to which a competent authority shall set the threshold referred to in paragraph 2(d).
EBA shall submit those draft regulatory technical standards to the Commission by 31 December 2014.
Power is delegated to the Commission to adopt the regulatory technical standards referred to in the first subparagraph in accordance with Articles 10 to 14 of Regulation (EU) No 1093/2010.
7. EBA shall issue guidelines on the application of this Article. Those guidelines shall be adopted in accordance with Article 16 of Regulation (EU) No 1093/2010.]]></comment>
<ownerDesignName>BIRD data models</ownerDesignName>
<parentDocument>C841613E-B205-A3DA-EAFA-A5DB8D0BE058</parentDocument>
</BIDocument>
