<?xml version = '1.0' encoding = 'UTF-8'?>
<Entity class="oracle.dbtools.crest.model.design.logical.Entity" directorySegmentName="seg_0" id="396D4ECD-8814-C66D-0F86-FC725364B83B" name="State and local government and Social security funds">
<createdBy>Dominik</createdBy>
<createdTime>2021-07-06 11:08:49 UTC</createdTime>
<commentInRDBMS><![CDATA[Regulation (EU) 549/2013:
State government (excluding social security funds) (S.1312)
2.115 Definition: this subsector consists of those types of public administration which are separate institutional units
exercising some of the functions of government, except for the administration of social security funds, at a level
below that of central government and above that of the governmental institutional units existing at local level.
Included in subsector S.1312 are those non-profit institutions which are controlled by state governments and
whose competence is restricted to the economic territories of the states.
Local government (excluding social security funds) (S.1313)
2.116 Definition: this subsector includes those types of public administration whose competence extends to only a local
part of the economic territory, apart from local agencies of social security funds.
Included in subsector S.1313 are those non-profit institutions which are controlled by local governments and
whose competence is restricted to the economic territories of the local governments.
Social security funds (S.1314)
2.117 Definition: the social security funds subsector includes central, state and local institutional units whose principal
activity is to provide social benefits and which fulfil each of the following two criteria:
(a) by law or by regulation certain groups of the population are obliged to participate in the scheme or to pay
contributions; and
(b) general government is responsible for the management of the institution in respect of the settlement or
approval of the contributions and benefits independently from its role as supervisory body or employer.
There is usually no direct link between the amount of the contribution paid by an individual and the risk to
which that individual is exposed.]]></commentInRDBMS>
<ownerDesignName>BIRD data models</ownerDesignName>
<shouldEngineer>false</shouldEngineer>
<engineerTo>
<item key="506C3777-4731-CD0A-8CFF-8965ED0252F3" value="false"/>
<item key="9D37A54F-1C11-31C4-737B-2F9B9E5FEEAE" value="false"/>
<item key="935F9DB7-5B1F-AD7A-2885-527EF3895C21" value="false"/>
<item key="95824C8F-787A-FE7E-FC6E-EB0A6A49B2A0" value="false"/>
<item key="E191B903-6A69-BF7E-025A-59418E56E39D" value="false"/>
<item key="70BBF9EB-559F-53F6-36C6-737D16EB7BDD" value="false"/>
<item key="AEFDAE93-361A-74FC-D9B0-896822C5F2BB" value="false"/>
</engineerTo>
<typeID>7A67499C-0479-82E2-9F82-A693B748701D</typeID>
<adequatelyNormalized>NO</adequatelyNormalized>
<expectedVolumes>0</expectedVolumes>
<fwdEngineeringStrategyName>Single Table</fwdEngineeringStrategyName>
<growthPercent>0</growthPercent>
<growthType>Year</growthType>
<hierarchicalParent>37AC7FD7-6B31-0934-1460-CD9A0DEB61B2</hierarchicalParent>
<maxVolumes>9999999</maxVolumes>
<minVolumes>0</minVolumes>
<normalForm>Third</normalForm>
<preferredAbbreviation>STT_LCL_GVRNMNT_SCL_SCRTY_FNDS</preferredAbbreviation>
</Entity>
