<?xml version = '1.0' encoding = 'UTF-8'?>
<Entity class="oracle.dbtools.crest.model.design.logical.Entity" directorySegmentName="seg_0" id="4A502F49-3E3C-81C4-5608-7F4401EDE34A" name="Deposit taking corporation">
<createdBy>Dominik</createdBy>
<createdTime>2021-07-07 10:17:56 UTC</createdTime>
<commentInRDBMS><![CDATA[Regulation (EU) No 549/2013, 2.75
Deposit-taking corporations except the central bank (S.122) 2.75 
Definition: the deposit-taking corporations except the central bank subsector (S.122) includes all financial corporations and quasi-corporations, except those classified in the central bank and in the MMF subsectors, which are principally engaged in financial intermediation and whose business is to receive deposits and/or close substitutes for deposits from institutional units, hence not only from MFIs, and, for their own account, to grant loans and/or to make investments in securities. 
2.76 Deposit-taking corporations except the central bank cannot be described simply as 'banks', because they may include some financial corporations which do not call themselves banks, or some financial corporations which are not permitted to do so in some countries, while some other financial corporations describing themselves as banks may not in fact be deposit-taking corporations. The following financial intermediaries are classified in sub- sector S.122: 
(a) commercial banks, 'universal' banks, 'all-purpose' banks; 
(b) savings banks (including trustee savings banks and savings banks and loan associations); 
(c) post office giro institutions, post banks, giro banks; 
(d) rural credit banks, agricultural credit banks; 
(e) cooperative credit banks, credit unions; 
(f) specialised banks (e.g. merchant banks, issuing houses, private banks); and 
(g) electronic money institutions principally engaged in financial intermediation. 
2.77 The following financial intermediaries are classified in subsector S.122 where it is their business to receive repayable funds from the public, whether in the form of deposits or in other forms such as the continuing issue of long-term debt securities: 
(a) corporations engaged in granting mortgages (including building societies, mortgage banks and mortgage credit institutions); 
(b) municipal credit institutions. 
Otherwise, financial intermediaries are classified in subsector S.124. 
2.78 Subsector S.122 does not include: 
(a) head offices which oversee and manage other units of a group consisting predominantly of deposit-taking corporations except the central bank, but which are not deposit-taking corporations. Such head offices are classified in subsector S.126;
(b) non-profit institutions recognised as independent legal entities serving deposit-taking corporations, but not engaged in financial intermediation. They are classified in subsector S.126; and 
(c) electronic money institutions not principally engaged in financial intermediation]]></commentInRDBMS>
<ownerDesignName>BIRD data models</ownerDesignName>
<shouldEngineer>false</shouldEngineer>
<engineerTo>
<item key="DAAC984B-B2E8-C145-BF34-9BFB502D9CBB" value="false"/>
<item key="0C783F40-7D13-738D-9D50-1050885C3D99" value="false"/>
<item key="4C82EC0E-87DF-70E2-243C-682AA3E09370" value="false"/>
<item key="83B1704A-A97A-C0A9-3158-32D1A66BF66B" value="false"/>
<item key="C514A9B1-F2A2-7294-2C10-7342CD541759" value="false"/>
<item key="49397F4F-33A8-CA4A-E717-66F5DB449882" value="false"/>
</engineerTo>
<typeID>7A67499C-0479-82E2-9F82-A693B748701D</typeID>
<adequatelyNormalized>NO</adequatelyNormalized>
<expectedVolumes>0</expectedVolumes>
<fwdEngineeringStrategyName>Single Table</fwdEngineeringStrategyName>
<growthPercent>0</growthPercent>
<growthType>Year</growthType>
<hierarchicalParent>874B5668-704D-E089-1B04-719A14DFD772</hierarchicalParent>
<maxVolumes>9999999</maxVolumes>
<minVolumes>0</minVolumes>
<normalForm>Third</normalForm>
<preferredAbbreviation>DPST_TKNG_CRPRTN</preferredAbbreviation>
</Entity>
